giftcardspromocodes.com 2018-03-25

# Privacy Policy | Amazon Gift Card Free Promo Codes

Welcome to the Privacy Policy page for [GiftCardsPromoCodes.com](http://giftcardspromocodes.com/). The privacy of our visitors to our is very much important to us.

For each unique visitor and unique page-views to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes information of your browser type, your IP address, City/State/Country. But we don’t collect your email address or your contact numbers at all. In this page we will tell what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit our site.  The information we collect here is used for internal review purpose only and we immediately discard that once we review that. This type of information is used to improve the content of our Web page and We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
As we stated that we collect your information and we do that by the mean of cookies to store your preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

**Ad Servers:**  
We are professional blogger and use third party advertisements on Gift Card Promo Codes blog. We try to provide interest based ads based on your previous and current history. We have relationships with other companies like Google ([www.google.com/adsense](http://www.google.com/adsense)) that we allow us to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policy of: <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>

If don’t want to give you information then you can disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings. Please make sure that deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program.  Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie might be added.

In case of any question regarding our privacy policy or term of condition then you can contact us by commenting here.

Updated:- 4th March, 2015

## Learn to get Free Gift Cards, vouchers, coupon codes and promotional offers from Amazon and eCommerce and local stores of US, Canada and UK.
